JENESSA WHITE

Front End Engineer









ienessawhite.com



Instilled with a passion for bringing beauty and ideal user experience to the web, I'm a Front-End Engineer. Using a suite of skills that I am continuously developing, I strive to bring positive and unique ideas that will enhance the products and services that we provide. My experience in customer service has provided me with an advantageous understanding of UI/UX.



EXPERIENCES

Project Manager - Rocket55 Jan 2017 - Present

Manage web development & design projects.

Create sitemaps for high-ranking SEO websites

Wireframe websites of all web developments, instituting a user-centered design (UCD) approach.

MDU Representative - DIRECTV May 2016 - September 2016

Provided customer with technical solutions for their DIRECTV equipment.

Coordinated with Research & Resolution and Tier 2 Technical Support teams on complex issues.

Protected customer's financial and personal data by adhering to the highest standards of security. Handled 20-40 customer calls/requests a day.

Registration Consultant - SportsEngine June 2015 - May 2016

Worked directly with clients to plan on how to meet needs and goals for their registration systems.

Built registration forms on the SportsEngine platform for clients.

Organized, revised and updated information on SportsEngine websites and registrations.

EDUCATION

The Iron Yard 2016-2017 University of Minnesota 2009-2014

Front-End Engineering

B.S Kinesiology

